[
  {
    "Front": "ναός (/νεώς)",
    "Back": " sb. 2 m.: tempel"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ναῦς",
    "Back": " sb. 3 f.: skib"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ναύτης",
    "Back": " sb. 1 m.: sømand"
  },
  {
    "Front": "νεκρός",
    "Back": " adj. 1-2: død"
  },
  {
    "Front": "νέµω",
    "Back": " vb.: fordeler"
  },
  {
    "Front": "νέος",
    "Back": " adj. 1-2: ny"
  },
  {
    "Front": "νῆσος",
    "Back": " sb. 2 f.: ø"
  },
  {
    "Front": "νίκη",
    "Back": " sb. 1 f.: sejr"
  },
  {
    "Front": "νοέω",
    "Back": " vb.: tænker"
  },
  {
    "Front": "νοµίζω",
    "Back": " vb.: mener"
  },
  {
    "Front": "νόµος",
    "Back": " sb. 2 m.: lov, fordeling"
  },
  {
    "Front": "νόσος",
    "Back": " sb. 2 f.: sygdom"
  },
  {
    "Front": "νοῦς",
    "Back": " sb. 2 m.: sind, tanke"
  },
  {
    "Front": "νῦν",
    "Back": " adv.: nu"
  },
  {
    "Front": "νύξ",
    "Back": " sb. 3 f.: nat"
  }
]